# JIAN GODITO

# FRONT END DEVELOPER

# CONTACT

☐ 09217228645

☐ Jgodito27@gmail.com

☐ https://jian-godito.vercel.app/

☐ B7 L16 Villa Jacinta, Laspina City.

# PROFILE

Hello, I'm Jian Godito and I'm 22 years old, currently living at Laspinas City. and I want to be a successful front-end developer someday, and i will continue learning to gain knowledge and to improve my skills to be a front-end developer

# **\rightarrow**

# SKILLS

- HTML
- JAVASCRIPT
- Bootstrap
- Tailwindcss
- CSS/SASS
- REACTJS
- REDUX
- TYPESCRIPT

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# FRONT END DEVELOPER

2022-Current

# **Innovations Group**

McDonald's

As a FRONTEND Developer of that company, Located at Pasay city, I am responsible for maintaining and Fixing errors of the websites or company projects. there are almost 100 websites to develop and need to maintain. And we use the waterfall method in our company First we need the requirements, Design, Implementation, and Verification. Maintenance. And System Testing and Deployment, Once you verify that your app is working, you're ready to deploy it. That's why i need to communicate to the tester to do the testing phase before we deploy the projects. And we used HTML, CSS3/Sass, JavaScript, ReactJS, And TypeScript to develop the projects.

Service Crew 2019-2021

# EDUCATION

Bachelor of science In Information Technology

#### STI COLLEGE

2018-2022



As a Part-time Service crew for 2 years, I need to manage my time work, and school because I want to be productive. And it helps me to support my finances as a student at that time. And I learned how to value my salary and manage it. And I also learned how to manage my time and work and to be productive.